//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"Which country has appeared in every world cup finals since the first in 1930?",
        answer: "Brazil",
        options:[
            "Brazil",
            "Argentina",
            "France",
            "Germany"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Who is the only player to win three World Cup?",
        answer: "Pele",
        options:[
            "Johan Cruyff",
            "Diego Maradona",
            "Alfredo Di Stefano",
            "Pele"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Who is the oldest player to play at the world cup finals?",
        answer: "Roger Milla",
        options:[
            "Roger Milla",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Pele",
            "Dino Zoff"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"Who player has the most captain appearences at the world cup?",
        answer: "Diego Maradona",
        options:[
            "Franz Beckenbauer",
            "Cafu",
            "Diego Maradona",
            "Lothar Matthaus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Whhich goal keeper holds recors for the most clean sheets at the world cup finals?",
        answer: "Peter Shilton",
        options:[
            "Iker Casillas",
            "Peter Shilton",
            "Manuel Neuer",
            "Taffarel"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"How many of the Netherlands' starting XI were booked at 2010 world cup finals",
        answer: "Eight",
        options:[
            "Four",
            "Six",
            "Eight",
            "Ten"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Luis Monti played World Cup finals for which two teams?",
        answer: "Argentina and Italy",
        options:[
            "Argentina and Italy",
            "Hungary and Russia",
            "Sweden France",
            "England and Scotland"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Who is the all most goal scorer in the World Cup finals?(16)",
        answer: "Miroslav Klose",
        options:[
            "Gerd Muller",
            "Ronaldo",
            "Pele",
            "Miroslav Klose"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"How many World Cup finals have won in the penalty shoot out?",
        answer: "Two",
        options:[
            "Five",
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"In Which city was the last time there was a crowd of over 100,000 in attendance for the final?",
        answer: "Mexico City",
        options:[
            "London",
            "Rio de Janeiro",
            "Moscow",
            "Mexico City"
        ]
    },
];